Hey there, Danny here. A few weeks ago,
a community post was posted where we ask
you to send in any questions you had for
the tunes. We happen to get a whole lot
more submitted than expected. So, if you
don't see yours answered just yet, don't
worry. A part two will be coming very
soon to answer the rest.
Do you consent to the Aiker extraction?
Have you ever told Dandy it may make you
uncomfortable or maybe painful? Does he
care?
>> I don't really think I'm allowed to
decline Dandy of something he wants.
It's Dandy's world and we're just living
in it. What I feel regarding Aker
extractions is irrelevant because in the
moment my body belongs to him. I'm sure
he does care about my well-being though.
>> That's a good boy. Is it painful for you
to do the extraction, Astro? What's it
feel like? Is it more torture or
pleasure?
>> It hurts a lot, but it also feels good.
It's a combination of pain and pleasure
that's hard to describe in words. But by
the end of the extraction, there's that
blissful feeling of the connection that
only Dandy and I have that overrides all
the hurt I felt during the experience.
So, it's not bad.
>> Why don't you use your tune ability more
considering you have the ability to
manipulate reality? Shouldn't it be
easier to not be a little [__]
>> I don't like rewriting moments in time
because then I won't really be living in
the moment. If I changed even one moment
for the better, I'm scared I would do it
again and again and start to rely on it
too much. And I think I'd get addicted.
Even if bad things come my way and I do
end up looking like a little [__] I
feel like I should learn to overcome
those kind of things myself.
>> Astro, do you love Dandy? Do you have
any other friends besides Dandy?
>> Oh, I love Dandy so so much. We're each
other's most bestest friends, but I love
everybody else, too. Sprout, Cosmo,
Roger, Boxton, V, Shelly, Goob, and even
Shrimpo. They're all my friends. I don't
know if they would say the same, but I
hope so.
>> My dearest Astro, do you think Danny
likes you or wants to have a
relationship with you?
>> Golly G. I know for sure he likes me,
but liking me more than just as a
friend. Well, I hope so. I know he's
aware of how I feel about him, and maybe
the reason it hasn't been reciprocated
is because a friend is all he'll ever
see me as. I'm still holding out hope
that maybe he has things he has to work
through before he can open up to me
fully.
>> Astro, is it possible you might
accidentally see other tunes
embarrassing dreams that reveal their
secrets? I
>> actually do know every tune's deepest,
darkest secrets through their
nightmares. Like how Razle has a fetish
for armpits and Dazzle really likes
feet. But I would never dare give any of
those secrets out. They're safe with me.
Many tunes like Yata Shrimpo and Sprout
have tried to get stuff out of me by
chasing my ass into back alleys to beat
me up, but I'm still holding strong.
>> Dear Astro, do you have trouble walking
through doors with your fat ass?
>> Not as much trouble as you might think.
Many tunes in Garden View were gifted by
the grace of Jesus Christ with big butt
cheeks. So Danny makes sure that
whenever new buildings are erected in
our lovely town of Garden View, the
doors will be customuilt to accommodate
for us or rather our cheeks. Why does
Dandy extract ickor off you?
>> While every tune is made up of ecore,
I'm the only tune whose body is
naturally producing more of it all the
time. Specifically behind my eye. So
every now and then I need it drained or
my head gets all heavy and I feel dizzy.
>> It's basically a period.
>> Basically.
>> Do you ever wash that blanket?
>> No. Other tunes don't like standing next
to me sometimes because it's dirty and
stinky, but it's kind of develop a smell
and texture I'm used to. I'm afraid if I
washed it, it would smell and feel
different and I would be uncomfy.
>> Dear Astro, will you ever fight back
when someone hurts you? It would depend
on what you mean by hurt. I can take a
slap and walk away and I'll try my best
to avoid a life or death situation. But
I can wreck a [__] if it comes down to
it because I'm always carrying a gun in
my butt crack legally, too, because I
have a legal carry permit.
>> Hey, Astro, what is the worst dream you
ever seen? I think Finn hurts himself a
lot before bed, and that carries over to
him hurting himself a lot in his dreams,
too. I don't like to watch those.
>> Hey, Astro, what does Dandy's armpits
smell like? Why do you like Dandy's
nasty, stinky, smelly socks? And can you
describe his stink?
>> Andy's stink is my most favorite smell
in the whole world. I was the first tune
ever created after him and Pebble, so I
stuck close by him for an uncomfortably
long time. Because of that, I've become
accustomed to calming myself down by
smelling him. You would think he smells
something like fresh cut flowers or
pollen, but I would say he smells more
like an oatmeal raisin cookie because of
the cologne he wears. So, his sweaty,
damp, wet socks smell like, well, a wet
and stinky oatmeal raisin cookie.
>> What's the stinkiest item you have?
>> Probably a pair of Dandy's tidy whies I
have hidden under my bed. He
accidentally left it at my house one
night at a sleepover after changing into
his PJs. Oh, but don't tell Dandy I said
that. He can't know. What do you see in
Danny? He's power- hungry, selfish,
homophobic, and he fingers your eyehole
without consent. So, why go after him
and not someone else?
>> I don't know why everyone keeps asking
me that. Danny isn't perfect. Okay, I
know that he can be mean sometimes, but
that's just because he's stressed over
things a lot. He's the face of Dandy's
world. People always make him out to be
some kind of monster when they don't
even know him. He never means to hurt
me. Most of the time, it's my fault for
pushing him too far anyway. If I didn't
matter to him, he wouldn't bother
keeping me around. He's super nice and
sweet when we're alone. It's just that
he doesn't have a need to show that side
of himself to others cause they're not
his best friend. I am Astro. What's it
like being the cutest tune in the world?
Why do you let everyone pick on you?
Your arms are very cute and highly
useful. Never be ashamed, baby girl.
>> Thank you for all the kind words, but I
don't think the tunes are being mean
when they physically or mentally assault
me for having four arms. I was the one
born different than them. And if hurting
me helps them ease their discomfort with
my existence, then assault away, I say.
I do tell myself in the mirror from time
to time, though, that my extra set of
arms are my best feature. Astro, how
freaky can you really get with all four
of your arms, despite the name freaky
forearms?
>> Well, on Halloween, it means I can dress
up as a forarmed alien or a four-ear
armed werewolf. And I'd say that's very
freaky.
>> Astro, you can look into dreams. So,
what do you do if you see a nightmare?
>> If I see a nightmare, I'll usually watch
it for a bit before giving them a nice
dream to counteract it. Like, a month
ago, Goob was having a nightmare where
he was a cave diver and he got stuck
upside down and in a crawl space and
couldn't get out. So, I turned it into a
dream by making it so the cave was
actually a bouncy castle. He was so
happy he peed the bed. But, if a tune
had wronged my ass that day, I'll make
the nightmare worse for them. Um, I
shouldn't say that. When someone will
die in their sleep, what kind of dream
do you give them?
>> Luckily, tunes are immortals, so I
haven't run into that problem just yet.
But I will probably give them a dream
where they fall off a cliff and die in
their dream at the same time as real
life, just cuz I think that would be
silly. Astro, how did you know you were
gay and that you like Dandy?
>> I've always just known and that Dandy
would be the one regardless of whether
or not it would ever be reciprocated.
>> Astro, what do you think about Dandy and
Dial's relationship? And are you jealous
of what they once had?
>> I'm not allowed to be jealous because
even though I knew Dandy long before
Dial did, Dial was more brave than I was
and he expressed his feelings of love
first. I respected that back then. I
could tell what they had was a genuine
love. Danny and I didn't talk much those
days. He was dating Dial because I
couldn't stand to be around them. So, I
would say I was jealous back then, but
it's hard to be jealous today when I'm
the one who won and Dial is basically a
petty [__] Dial can stay mad while
Dandy keeps coming back to me.
>> Hey, Astro, do you stalk Dandy's dreams?
>> I try to give every tune an equal amount
of care when watching over their dreams.
But I can't deny I watch over Dandes
just a tad bit closer. And if he's not
dreaming about me, I'll typically find a
way to sneak myself in. He knows I do
that though and is happy about it
because he loves to have me around. So,
I wouldn't call it stalking.
>> Astro, I was wondering which of the guys
in Garden View do you find most
attractive and which one do you find
least attractive?
>> Oh gosh, I can't deny that there are
many attractive tunes in Garden View. Of
course, I have a bias for Dandy. He's
short, handsome, and difficult to look
away from. But I'll sometimes catch
myself looking at the tall tunes from
afar, too. like Dial Boxton and Razzle
and Dazzle. The lanky fellas like Lou
and Finn are nice to look at, too. And
also the lean ones like Boxton and
Sprout. And the fat ones like Rudy and
Squirm must be so soft. Don't tell
anyone I said all this.
>> Sprout, I got to ask, what would you do
if Dandy was taller than you and started
calling you a dweeb? Well, obviously I'd
break his legs so that he'd be shorter
than me again. Nobody. and I mean nobody
is allowed to be taller than me in
Garden View. Like 90% of my control
comes from me literally looking down on
other tunes. Why do you always wear this
scarf? Because I'm cold. What do you
think, dork? I walk around naked, no
coat or nothing. Hey, Sprout. How did
you not question why Cosmo suddenly had
four arms when you kissed Astro in the
dark attic? Was it just the urge of
wanting to do it so badly with Cosmo
that it blindsided you? To be honest, I
thought it was just Cosmo wrapping his
legs around my waist cuz he can be a
little freaky girly boy like that. Do
you still remember that night when you
and Roger and Dandy were being guards
for the night and you and Dandy kissed?
If so, what do you think about that
moment? Oh. Uh, well, I mean, I try not
to think of that moment, but I'm still
haunted by it for obvious reasons. like
because Dandy is a [__] and now I have
to go the rest of my life knowing I
kissed a [__] and I still don't know
why he did it. Like if he likes me or
some [__] that I'd be confusing as hell
because he always says he's not gay and
[__] and I know Astro still has it out
for me since he saw the whole thing and
I've been having nightmares for a full
year straight. It has to be Astro's
doing. How come you aren't mayor of
Garden View? You're a vastly more
capable leader than Dandicus though that
isn't saying much since you're still a
tune. That's what I've been saying. I
don't know. Tunes are stupid. They don't
know how good they could have it if they
elected me as their leader instead of
Dandy. I'm skinny. That's how you know
I'm a good person. Dandy is fat, which
is probably why every other tune is
getting fat, too, cuz he can't control
them. We should have never let Squirm
into town. I do not like fat tunes. They
piss me off. Except for Cosmo. Sprout,
do you still hate Dandy? Is water wet?
Does poop come from a butt? I don't hate
Dandy. He's my rival more than anything.
When I put him down, it's because I know
it makes him stronger and a better
leader. He's my rival more than
anything. Hey, Sprout, how was that
strawberry milkshake tasted? I try not
to think about it cuz it was a very dark
day for me. So, thanks for bringing it
back up, [__] It tasted better than
any other goddamn milkshake I've ever
had, which sickens me to my gay
strawberry core. Sprout, are the dots on
your cheeks like freckles, or are they
seeds? How the hell should I know? What
even are freckles? I'm a strawberry. I
can take them off. So, seeds, I don't
know. I don't give a [__] Sprout, would
you ever slap Dandy's big butt? Um,
yeah. You know that thing jiggles
aggressively. Sprout, do you love me?
I'm your biggest fan. Also, how did you
feel when Dandy kissed you in episode 2?
Also, can I have a cupcake, please? I
love all my fans because unlike loser
tunes like Dandy, I've actually got
fans. And well, for the first few
seconds he was kissing me, I was like
angry at my life for how it somehow lead
to a point where I would kiss someone
beneath me. Then I got even more angry
that Dandy wasn't a bad kisser. I'm just
happy that Cozmo wasn't there to see.
Not that Cozmo and I are boyfriends or
anything. We're just best buds, baking
buddies. I'll be giving out free
cupcakes in the back alley across the
street out of my pickup truck if anyone
wants them.
Dear Sprout, do you support
homosexuality?
Well, I support myself being gay, but I
don't know if I'd say the same for
others. We all know Dandy is in the
closet cuz he's scared of what the world
would think. And so, I'd prefer the
world to stay a bit homophobic because
it makes Dandy's life worse, and that's
funny to me. Have you spoken with Louis
since Cozmo told him to unalive himself
over the phone? Louie constantly tries
to call or text, but Cosmo always
deletes his messages before I can read
them for some reason. Also, Louie lives
like three houses down, so it's hard to
get in contact with him. And I think
Louie is scared to walk by our
strawberry home because Cosmo shot him
that one time.
Sprout, why do you act all sweet to
Cozmo, then go abuse him? Like, you two
would have the cutest moment, then next
thing I know, you're beating him black
and blue. I'm sweet with him cuz he's my
little boy toy. What you should be
asking is why Cosmo does things to make
me mad. I give that Swiss roll
everything. I let him live in my
strawberry home and he only pays almost
all of the rent and does all the cooking
and cleaning. The few times I do beat
him, it's warranted. In fact, I should
be beating him more often. Sprout, at
some point, will you stop being a [__]
with Cozmo? You've got to set him free.
Cozmo knows what he's signing up for.
You don't. So, sit down or I'll hit you,
too. I've learned from early on that
anything can be solved with a [__]
slap. When are you going to ask Cosmo to
marry you? Oh, well, I uh uh well uh
what makes you think I wouldn't want to
be the uh be the one proposed to? I
mean, in a lifelong friend kind of way
since we're best friends and that's it.
If you ate a strawberry, would it count
as cannibalism? Yeah, it would basically
be like I'm eating a tiny version of me
in which others couldn't hear its
screams. But I can I can talk to
strawberries. Sprout, are you the bottom
or is it Cosmo? I sleep on the top of
the bunk bed and Cosmo sleeps on the
bottom. We sleep that way so that if an
intruder ever breaks in to kidnap one of
us in the middle of the night, they will
grab Cosmo first. And so I will have
time to plan a course of action. Whether
that means me fighting back or just
getting my fat ass out of there. Sprout,
can you get Cosmo pregnant?
>> I'm willing to bet like $5 in a bucket
of tater tots that I most certainly
could since Dial brought up to me one
day out of the blue that strawberries
and Swiss rolls have much more
biological similarities than one might
expect. But I feel like our offspring
would look like some freakish hellspawn
abomination because his head is too long
sideways and my head is too long the
other way. I can't even imagine how
horribly ugly it would be with our
clashing jeans. Sprout, do you want kids
with Cosmo? I would only entertain the
idea if it's Cosmo who's carrying. Even
then, I worry that because babies are
small and because they would naturally
both be food, Cosmo would accidentally
eat them within the first year because
he's fat. Sprout, have you ever thought
if Cosmo was stolen from you?
>> Yeah, like what I just talked about with
the bunk beds. If someone stole Cozmo
and was running away with him down the
street, I'll probably chase after the
perpetrator for a couple minutes before
stopping and going back home. Cozmo is
fat and I know whoever stole him will
get tired and drop him eventually and
Cozmo will find his way back home
somehow. If we're talking about him
finding a new best friend, though,
that's not going to happen. He knows I
don't got anyone else. Sprout, do you
actually love Cozmo? Uh, love is a
strong word. I need to hear Cozmo say it
first before I give a concrete answer.
Who do you think is the most dominant in
your friendship/ relationship with
Cozmo? Well, obviously that would be me.
I think Cozmo and I could both see just
how much bigger I am than him when I go
twisted. And by nature's law, the bigger
one is the dominant one. Everybody knows
that.
>> First question for Dandy. Why do you
blush sometimes at Astro? Do you like
him? You're very sus, buddy. What are we
trying to allude to here? It's not that
I'm blushing. If it looks like my face
is red, that's just my photosynthesis
acting up.
>> Dear Danny, do you like Astro back as a
boyfriend?
>> Boyfriends? Who told you that? Was it
Astro? We're not boyfriends. He's uh
just my best friend. Nothing more. That
would be gay if you were my boyfriend.
>> Hey Dandy, this question is for you. And
I was wondering, do you ever go to party
alone or do you always bring Astro? You
know, since he's your best friend. If
I've got someplace I need to be, I'll
always make sure Astro is going to have
been invited. Also, if he isn't, I'm
taking him with me or I'm not going.
Honestly, we're so close. I don't even
have to ask anymore. He'll just ask
where we're going today.
>> Dandy, why do you take Ekor from Astro?
What do you do with it? And how much
have you taken?
>> So many buckets full. Astro's body
naturally produces a whole lot of Aker
that accumulates in his eye. It's like
there's a fountain going off in there
nonstop. If no one breaks the seal and
lets some of that acre drain out, it's
going to give Astro a headache and it's
too painful for him to do it himself.
So, I do what I can to help and make him
feel good while doing it. As for what I
do with the icker, that's a secret. Just
know it's not going to waste behind the
scenes.
>> Andy, did you know whenever Astro cleans
your socks, he actually smells them?
>> What? No, Astro wouldn't do that. He's
just being a good pal, a friend. That
would just be weird. You're weird for
suggesting that. I did notice like nine
pairs of socks have gone missing this
week, though.
>> One, be honest. Are you gay, Dandy? Two,
would you like Astro to be your fanboy?
>> How many times do I have to tell you
people that I'm not a a boy liker? See,
I can't even say the word gay. And I
don't even know what a fanboy is. How am
I supposed to answer that? Are you
saying like Astro in minikrt and thigh
high socks and wearing cat ears? I guess
that would be kind of cool.
>> Dear Dandy, what had caused you to break
up with Dial? I know that you're
homophobic, but how did you actually
become homophobic? There was a time
where I mistakenly thought two boys
could be together and that it could be
normal. It was when I was dating Dial
and I was super happy almost all the
time. But then he and I started fighting
everyday because we were both always
working and society was judging us for
being both men when we just wanted to be
alone. and he talked too much about his
interests while not paying attention to
any of mine. And and I realized there's
no way two boys could be together cuz if
it didn't work for me, the star of the
show, who could be so delusional to
think it could work for anyone else?
>> Danny, do you ever think about dating
Dial again?
>> So, I can hear him go on and on about
trains for hours. I'll pass. I got the
Bible to read instead now.
>> Danny, how many times a week do you clog
your toilet?
>> Like two times a day. So, 14 times a
week.
>> Question for Dandy. If you have to
choose a tune that's so annoying that
you want them to be gone, who's that
tune?
>> Easy, Sprout. He has some nerve talking
back to me the way he always does. He
thinks he can get away with anything
just cuz he's the sexiest tune in Garden
View.
>> Dandy, why did you make out with Sprout?
>> I don't know. Sometimes I just do
things, okay? It was a spur-ofthe-
moment thing.
>> Dandy, can you stop eating food? It
makes you fat. I am Dandicus Dancifer. I
can eat whatever food I want whenever I
want.
>> Dear Dandy, can you explain why it's a
sin to be gay?
>> I don't got an explanation and I don't
need one because God himself said so in
Leviticus 18:22. Male tune shall do not
relations with a male tune as one does
with a female tune. That is detestable.
>> Dear Dandy, do you regret smooching
Astro?
>> No. I kissed him that one time as a
joke. That's all. And even though I got
on my knees and cried to God afterwards
for forgiveness, I think Astro liked it.
Sometimes I think about how I could kiss
Astral a whole lot more and maybe I'd
still be led into heaven if I forgive
God for a lifetime worth of sins right
before I died on my deathbed. But then
there's the fear that I'd do something
gay and sinful only to die in a freak
accident right after. Then I'd go to
hell.
>> Dear Dandy, would you ever kiss Sprout?
And why? I mean, as long as it's not
like in a gay way, I guess I would be
down to do it again. He was the better
kisser between us last time, and I've
been practicing with myself in the
mirror. In case a moment like that ever
came up again, I've got to show him how
good I can really be.
>> Andy, why do you say you are not gay,
but you kiss boys?
>> Sometimes things are just out of my
control. I'm not to blame for all those
times I kissed boys. A kiss is a
two-party act, after all. Just because
I've done it like 30 times doesn't make
me not straight.
>> Dear Dandy, what do you think of Astro?
And if you were to love someone, who
would it be?
>> Astro is my best friend. And I've
thought long and hard about the type of
tune I'd like to fall in love with. And
for one, I know they would have to be
taller than me, like how Astro is since
I already struggle to reach things in my
house. Also, they'd have to be my best
friend first and foremost, like Astro,
and be able to take care of Pebble when
I'm away. Just like how Pebble is
familiar with Astro's scent, an extra
pair of arms like Astro would also be
cool. And also, I would like their
breath to smell like Astros since Astro
tasted really good when I kissed him
that one time.
>> A question for Dandy. What do you do in
your free time?
>> You wouldn't know it about me, but I
like going to different public bathrooms
around Garden View and [__] and then
writing down my experience on Yelp. I
don't know if anybody is reading my
reviews, but I like to think I'm putting
good content out in the world.
>> Dandy, would you let Astro top you?
>> I think even without saying anything,
Astro and I both know he would be the
bottom no matter what. If Dial could
never talk me into being a bottom for
him when we were together, then there's
no way Astro could.
>> Dandy, did you enjoy peeing in Sprout's
mouth that one time?
>> I sure did. And I would do it all over
again if it's to save his life. I don't
like the guy, but he's my rival. If
anyone is going to want to alive him,
it's not going to be thirst. And I think
he knew that, too. That if I was ever
out of water and was going to die, I
could only ask for Sprout to pee in my
mouth, too. It was weird when he came to
my house a week later and asked me to
pee in his mouth again, though. He said
the water had been turned off by Garden
View, which is weird cuz I'm the mayor
of Garden View and I never turned the
water off. I peed in like nine bottles
and gave them to him. And then he came
back to my house seven more times after
that along with Roger Blood and Squirm
who also said their water was turned
off.
>> So, uh, Astro and Dandy, why do y'all
have big cheeks?
>> Because us tunes were meticulously
designed to be the perfect beings. Our
perfect butts reflect that.
>> Dear Dandy, why do you and Sprout hate
each other?
>> I don't know what Sprout's deal is. He
says we're rivals just because we're
both plants. And he's mean to me and
goes on and on about how much more
popular he is than me despite me being
the main character of Dandy's World. To
be completely honest, I don't know what
his deal is. I think he's just jealous.
>> Dandy, what's a secret about Sprout he'd
hate for you to share? That cosmo dick
is way bigger than his is, but they both
walk around without pants and everyone
can see it, so I don't really know if
it's much of a secret.
>> Dandy, how many exes do you have?
>> Dial is the only tune I've ever been
with and I don't see myself getting with
another tune anytime soon. I don't think
I'll ever be able to find someone as
good as Dial. When it was bad, it was
bad, but when it was good, it was great.
I'd rather stay alone than risk losing
someone like him again. Dear Dandy, when
will you get with Astro? I saw you take
that are you gay test and I know you
gay.
>> Just because a gay test told me I'm gay,
it doesn't mean I'm gay. It just means
that I have some gay thoughts, which
makes sense because I parttook in the
gay lifestyle for too long. I just have
to keep suppressing my lingering gayness
and they will go away eventually.
>> Dandy, rank all the kisses you had in
these episodes and tell us which one was
the best.
>> Oh [__] Let's see. That would be a
Dial, Astro, Sprout, Shrimpo, and Louie,
right? Wow, that's uh a lot of boy
tunes. Uh well, Louie might be at the
bottom since that was basically like
kissing a balloon. Shrimpo was forceful
with his. I didn't like that. So,
between Astro Sprout and Dial, I think
Astro would be below the other two only
because I could feel he's holding back.
Maybe because he knows I'm holding
myself back, too. I don't know. All the
times I used to kiss Dial felt natural.
And screw it. Yeah, Sprout is the best
kisser in Garden View. But don't tell
that strawberry [__] I said that.
Dear Cosmo, are you being held captive
by Sprout? Tell them what I told you to
say, [__] Not at all. Sprout is my
best friend. I'm exactly where I want to
be. The reason for the collection of
collars and leashes around the house is
because that's what he uses to walk me
around with to make sure I get my walks
in for the day. Because I'm lazy without
him. I can go wherever I want to as long
as I have my location finder turned on
my phone and as long as I don't leave
Sprout's front yard. Cosmo, are you
Sprout's pet? Would it be so bad if I
was? Is a tune being another Toon's pet
really even a bad thing or is it just
part of the tune life cycle we all have
to go through at some point? Dear Cosmo,
is your icing a part of your body, or is
it something you have to reapply? It's a
part of my body because I'm a freak of
nature. Whenever Sprout is low on icing,
he'll even just take a scoop off my head
and the icing will slowly grow back
after a couple hours. Dear Cosmo, are
you a thick boy or a skinny legend? It
depends on the season. During summer, I
try and make myself lose a few pounds
because I'm insecure of my natural
chubbiness. But whenever fall and winter
roll around, I really rack up the pounds
because I love me some holiday cookies.
I remember one time it was snowing
outside and to keep warm, Sprout was
cuddling up next to my fat body on the
couch. Sprout slapped my thighs and
pointed out, "It sounds like slapping a
water balloon." Since then, he calls my
thighs his thickies. He also doesn't let
me go on a diet because he likes me
being soft. So, I guess you could say
I'm heavy even by Swiss roll standards.
If that answers your question, dear
Cosmo, what kind of current relationship
do you have with Sprout? Sprout is my
best friend and best baking buddy. I
don't think you can get any closer than
that, but I wouldn't have it any other
way. Dear Cosmo, what do you like to
bake the most? My favorite thing to bake
is my world famous double chunk
chocolate cookies. I'm a huge fan of the
Costco guys, and I would love for them
to come to Garden View just to give my
cookies five big booms. Cosmo, do you
get beaten by sprout frequently? What
kind of question is this? Not frequently
enough to fret over. It's usually twice.
Once in the morning and again right
before bed. But if Sprout finds out I
did something I wasn't supposed to like,
leave the toilet seat up. I'll be woken
up by a punch or two. It's fine though.
Dear Cosmo, do you ever think of leaving
him because of how he acts? Or stay with
him despite the things he had done to
you? Leave who? Who do I have to leave?
And what have they done to me? Do you
get beat up sometimes? Cosmo, blink
twice if you need help. Blink three
times if you're held in an abusive house
with a strawberry guy. The [__]
I know you're not about to blink, [__]
Hey, Cosmo, listen. We're all pretty
worried about you. Don't you think you
have a pretty strange relationship with
Sprout? From the outside, it looks like
you often have to go to extremes and do
the wrong things just to please him.
It's a very contradictory relationship,
even though it's noticeable that Sprout
also cares about you a lot. By the way,
I love you. Huh? worry about me. You
really don't have to. Sprout and I are
best friends, so everything's okay. I
know he can be a little intense
sometimes, but he's only like that
because he cares a lot. I don't mind
doing things for him if it makes him
happy. Besides, I mess up a lot, so it's
only fair that I try harder, right?
Really, there's no reason to worry about
me, but um thank you for caring about me
and thank you for saying you love me,
too. That made me really happy. Dear
Cosmo, how is your cake so absolutely
geographically humongously stunningly
amazingly oversized and peachely shaped?
Are you talking about my fat dump truck
of an ass? I guess I just got lucky when
I was being designed. I've been told
quite often that I've got the biggest
ass in Garden View, which is quite a
special feeling. Cosmo, do you have a
map? Because I get lost into your eyes.
Oh, don't tell Sprout. Otherwise, he's
going to get jealous and hit me. Cosmo,
why do you and Sprout kiss and mate?
People are now shipping you. Wait, is
kissing not a common thing friends do
with each other? Then why is Sprout so
adamant about doing it with me all the
time? Cosmo, do you actually like when
Sprout pisses on you? Yes, it is wet and
warm. Why do you hold your head with one
hand all the time? Like, you don't move
your hand at all while moving? Is it
because your head is so [__] big that
you need to hold it? Little [__] cake
boy. My head weighs 234 lbs. If I don't
hold it sometimes, I could topple over
and some other tune would be smashed
like a pumpkin. That reference wasn't
just random. It's how Gord's parents
died. Both of them. Nobody has told him
yet. Why are you called Cosmo? You're
like a Twinkie or some [__] Your name
should be Twink. I'm actually a Swiss
roll, not a Twinkie. As for why I'm
called Cosmo, that's because before I
got a name, I used to eat a lot of
cosmic brownies because I'm a fatty. And
so everyone called me Cosmo and the name
just sort of stuck. Hey, why do you
always keep Sprout side even though he
does bad things to his friends? What is
every stupid question going to be about
me? Well, I would argue others are
usually the ones starting conflict with
him first, not the other way around. And
Sprout's my best friend. Naturally, I'm
always going to take his side regardless
because that's what friends do for each
other. God forbid I sided with another
tune. I'd be sleeping on the couch. Who
do you think is the most dominant in
your friendship/ relationship with
Sprout? Does it look like Sprout is the
more dominant one? I hope so. I like it
that way. Cosmo and Sprout in the pool
episode. Why did you guys beat up Astro
with rolling pins? Oh, yeah. That
happened. Sprout didn't want to do it,
but I managed to talk him into doing
what needed to be done. That moment
taught me I have a bit more sway in our
friendship than I thought. We had to
teach Astro that tricking a strawberry
to suck up another strawberry isn't
funny. How do you sleep with that big
ass head, Cosmo? I don't. Most nights I
topple out of bed. Okay, so like why do
you let Sprout walk all over you when
you can obviously fight back? Well, the
way I see it, Sprout isn't walking all
over me. He's running around on a leash,
too. As long as he's holding the other
end. Cosmo, what do you cook for the
Garden View tunes? Do you and Ginger get
along? When I'm not baking sweets, I
like cooking up a mean batch of sloppy
joe's to share with the tunes when we
get together in the park. I actually
just did two weeks ago, and I ran into
Ginger there. I used to be a whole lot
closer to Ginger before I came out of
the closet at a family dinner. She tried
to disown me and Sprout got so mad that
he punched her with all his strawberry
strength and blew off half her face. We
still try to be friendly since we're
cousins, but it will never be the same
since I know how she views me.
>> Dear Dial, does your head actually tell
the time?
>> Yes. Dial, do you miss Dandy? And if you
had the option to date him again, would
you go for it?
>> I most certainly would reenter a
relationship with Dandy. I often think
to myself how nice it would be if he
would even just call me back from time
to time. He's well aware of my still
lingering feelings for him, and I'm
afraid that's what makes things quite
awkward between us.
>> Dial, what was it like dating Dandy, if
you don't mind the question?
>> It was the only time I was ever really
happy, I suppose. And to this day, I yet
to see Dandy any happier than when he
was with me as well. We fought a lot and
his favorite thing to say to me was that
we wouldn't last because we're so
similar when we get mad. And when he
screams at me, it's like he's screaming
at himself. I liked our fights because
it meant we were both passionate about
keeping things going. When I didn't
argue back one day, I think that's when
he felt I wasn't serious. But he's
wrong. Dial, are you jealous of Astro
because Dandy is closer with him?
>> It is not jealousy, but disgust when I
see them together. When Dandy and I were
dating, Dandy was more put together like
me. But since our relationship ended,
he's reverted back to the gremlin of
which I knew before he and I dated,
where he sees tunes like Astro as just
another toy he can use and abuse. And
Astro is quite possibly the worst tune
to pair up with that, a depressed loner
who would let Dandy get away with
destroying the whole world if it means
making Dandy happy because he himself
has nothing. If I were in Astro's place,
I wouldn't enable Dandy's maniacal
spiraling. He would either grow or lose
me again, but he would not stay as he
is.
>> Dear Dial, rumor has it that Dandy
doesn't really like you because of your
popularity. How do you two get along
when the cameras are off? By the way, I
am a big fan of you.
>> I can assure you there are many reasons
as to why Dandy isn't fond of me these
days. Most of the reasons being rather
silly. I do wish we were closer if he
would only allow it. But he's the star
of the show and he decides what tunes he
has around him. I am not one of those
tunes because he has been losing IQ
points by the day since our breakup.
>> Dial, do you like My Little Pony? Who is
your favorite character? My Little Pony
is a guilty pleasure of mine, I'll
admit. Despite it being a cartoon
primarily targeted towards young girls,
I do have a favorite pony, a stallion
specifically. It's embarrassing to say
it aloud like this, but it would have to
be Saurin. He's a Pegasus, and I find
his character arc and romance with the
cow pony Brayburn to be quite nice.
Saurin is 50 years old, which I can
relate to myself being up there in age.
that's twice as old as his boyfriend
Brayburn. But Brayburn still loves him
for who he is. And Saurin doesn't feel
worthy of his love. And he goes through
this big character arc where he fights
Twilight Sparkle. And Twilight Sparkle
uses a twisted magic spell to
accidentally turn Saurin into this evil
alicorn villain. And he almost loses his
mind until Brayburn saves him using the
power of gay love. Saurin seals his
magic away out of fear of it overtaking
him again. But later, it's revealed that
a fragmented piece of his magic broke
off from him and become a villain by
itself. And its goal is to group back up
with the rest of Saurin's magic that
Saurin had hidden away. And the only way
to not let that happen is for Saurin to
retake control of his magic again. But
this time when he does, he becomes the
alicorn of spacetime. And he gets his
own dimension called the sky train. that
is like a subway he can use to travel
anywhere throughout time that he wants.
That's one of my favorite details that
Saurin gets a train. I don't know why
Saurin doesn't use his time travel
powers or visit the sky train more
often, but I head cannon. It's because
Saurin is so scared of using his magic
again because it can easily overtake
him.
Sorry, I'm talking too much. I also ship
Apple Bottom and Care package. They're
really cute together, too. Dear Dial, do
you still miss Dandy? And how did it
feel when he dumped you on your
birthday?
>> Yes, I was dumped on my birthday and it
was humiliating. Sometimes I dream about
us getting back together and I dump him
on his birthday as revenge. But of
course, I can't do that if we're never
going to get back together in the first
place.
>> Dial, is it your fault Dandy's straight?
if that's what Dandy claims. But for a
tune who claims I turned him straight,
he sure spends an awful lot of time
flirting with exclusively male tunes.
Every time I see him, he's staring at
Louis big balloon butt cheeks and
kissing Astro or Sprout. It's kind of
funny, honestly. If you're going to
blame me for making you straight, maybe
stop acting like your type is still men.
Just saying.
>> Dear Dial, do you bother playing a game
of Kiss, Mary, Kill? Your tunes are
Sprout, Astro, and Dandy. I would kiss
Dandy to remind him of what he had lost.
It would be a fleeting one, like a
butterfly landing on his lips for just a
second. I would marry Sprout because
while he can be a troubling tune, his
home life with Cosmo is shockingly well
put together. And I would kill Astro by
tying each of his four arms to four
different trains going in all different
directions. And then I would start up
all the trains at the exact same time
and watch as he's torn apart, taking
bets with other tunes on which arm is
coming off first.
>> Hey dial, on a scale of 1 to 10, how
infatuated are you with trains? Is the
train collecting a side hobby or is it a
job?
>> 10. It's both a hobby and a job. I run
all six trains at Garden View Station
and when I get home, I spend my evenings
painting and playing with my model
trains. Other tunes always ask why I'm
so obsessed with them. I suppose it's
because my trains are dependable. No
matter how far I send them away, they
always come back because I'm the one in
control of them. These days, I don't
have control over much else.
>> Dear Dial, what shampoo do you use for
your chain?
>> Shampoo is for hair. This chain and
really my whole entire naked body
because it's made of the same material
gets premium railway grade lubricant
rubbed all over it before bed every
night. Same stuff I trust on my trains
back at the station. If it's good enough
for them, it's good enough for me.
>> Dear Dial, what is your favorite movie?
And if you had a real train, like a real
one, would you run over Shrimpo with it?
>> I don't watch many movies. Rather, I'll
watch the security cameras at the Garden
View Railway Station whenever I'm bored.
And on the rare chances I'm lucky, I'll
catch a tune or two sneaking in where
they shouldn't, and I'll blast one of
the train horns to scare them away. That
amuses me. Funny enough, Shrimpo is the
one tune I rarely see, but would
certainly like to. I've tried leading
Shrimpo to the Garden View Railway
Station numerous times to try and tie
him down to a track and run him over and
be done with him, but he always claims
to get tired on the long walk there and
turns back to go home. I think he's come
to figure out what it is I would like to
do to him.
>> Dial, do you still wear the underwear
that has Dandy's face on it?
>> I will not be humiliated for wearing a
highquality pair of underwear just
because they have my ex's sigil on them.
Where do you buy your eyeshadow?
>> Glisten often asks me that because he
doesn't believe me when I tell him that
this is just my natural look. He thinks
I shop at some secret store. Funny how
he has to pay $79.99
to mimic even a fraction of my natural
aura in a battle I wasn't even aware was
going on between us.
>> Dial, where do you go when everyone's
gone to bed at night?
Sometimes in the middle of the night, I
will go to Taco Bell and order just a
big box of tacos and eat them in the
parking lot and cry about things before
I go home to poop in my toilet because
Taco Bell gives Daddy Dial the shits.
>> Dial, if you could do anything, and I
mean anything in the world, what would
it be?
>> Have sex with Dandy again. And this
time, I would be the one on top. I never
got to be on top because he never let
me.
>> Dial. Has Dandy ever chucked Pebble at
you during a disagreement?
>> He's certainly tried to. Dandy is a
nefarious little flower. Fortunately for
both Pebble and myself, Pebble is far
too heavy for Dandy to be able to lift
off the ground.
>> Dial, is there anyone you'd be
interested in dating other than Dandy?
>> I've certainly thought about dating
again. As in dating a tune, Dandy has
his eyes set on just to break Dandy's
little heart. Dandy will never admit it
since going back in the closet. But I
see how he craves Astro. Oh, if I could
steal Astro away before Dandy could even
have a taste of him and let myself be
impregnated and carry Astro's children,
the hurt in Dandy's eyes would be
sublime.
>> Dial, what is your favorite train model
or type? Oh, that's an easy one. My
favorite has to be the 46010-wheeler
steam locomotive. It's such a classic
and I love the sound of the whistle.
You've no doubt seen them as they're the
model used around the holiday season.
You know, the little steam train that
loops around the Christmas tree. Every
time I see one of those little [__]
I have to stop and watch it go around
for a while.
>> Dial, are you a pro pole dancer? I've
never tried it, but I do believe I have
the upper body strength to pull it off.
And I admittedly do have the figure for
it, what with my childbearing hips and
all. I bet I could earn a lot of money
performing, but I don't know how often
tunes are looking to hire pole dancers
at their birthday parties.
>> Dial, why can't you just date Boxton?
You two are the most locked in tunes in
Garden View.
>> Something about him doesn't sit quite
right with me. A lot of his kindness
seems performative and I hate
performative [__]
>> Dial, what is your deepest fear?
>> Though I make it a habit to keep others
at a distance right now, I would hate to
die alone and for no one to mourn me
when I'm gone.
>> Dear Dial, why is your pants always
ripped? Also, do you miss dating Danny
at all?
>> I believe I already talked about Dandy
enough. As for why my pants are always
ripped, well, when you're packing an
entire bakery, it's difficult to go
through a whole entire day without the
backside of my pants bursting open. It's
happened so often that I'm not ashamed
to go about the rest of my day with my
ass exposed. The tunes of Garden View
are aware of this problem I have, and
they don't seem offended at it. It also
means they at least get a nice view
until I return home. Dial, I love you.
You've always been my favorite
character. Would you want to go on a
train date?
>> I've always dreamed about something like
that for a long time. Just me and
another tune riding an old sleeper train
through the Garden View countryside,
watching the fields roll by while the
sun sets outside the window.
>> Dial, how's the Lego train set?
>> Unfortunately, unsalvageable since Goo
got into the Legos and chewed them all
up.
Goob, what is your favorite Lego piece
to chew on? The railroad pieces from
Dial's new train set. The long gray ones
for the tracks are super chewable. Dial
keeps saying, "Please stop doing that,
Goob." And that just makes me want to
run away with the pieces and chew on
them more. Dear Goo, what's your
favorite word in your AAC unit? Oh,
that's a hard question. When I say
cookie or donut, someone will usually
give me a cookie or donut right after.
But I also like saying hello because
then it entices whoever I'm with to say
hello back. I like all the words. Goob,
how come your hair/ fur looks so fluffy?
Is it naturally fluffy or is that just
how it is? P.S. You're my favorite
character. Thank you. You're my favorite
character, too. This is just my natural
state, which makes for a lot of trouble
at home because Scraps says I shed too
much. I get fluffier and fluffier the
longer I go without bathing, too. I like
doing that cuz then it means I can hide
things like fidget spinners and squish
toys in my chest fluff and I'll forget
they're in there until they fall out.
Dear Goo, what happened after Scraps
killed Roger? Is she in jail or what?
Bye, buddy. I don't want my sister to go
to jail because then I will have one
less friend. Scraps had to give Roger so
much money for him to not report her to
the police for manslaughter. So much so
that she had to sell our house and we're
back to living on the streets. But we'll
get by. We always do. Dear Goob, do you
still live with Roger? I did live with
him for about a week, but then Roger
told me to get out because he values the
alone time. He says if we're living in
the same house, I'm going to be
bothering him. I don't take that
personally because Roger's a detective.
He needs a lot of time to sleep. And
well, let's just say that during that
week, neither of us were getting any
sleep at night. Goob, what is your
favorite color? I like red and blue
because they're the color of my hands.
And I know good things are going to come
when I put them out in front of me
because it means I get to reach out and
hug someone with them. I also like pink
because it makes me think of Shrimpo.
Dear Goob, what's your favorite flavor
of soda? Sometimes I pee in a bottle and
wait for my pee to cool and then I'll
pour it over ice. If I'm feeling extra
fun, I will pee in a bottle of sparkling
water and drink it while it's still
warm. That's basically soda. Hey Gooby
Goober, are you gay? If so, who do you
like? I don't know what gay means, but
other tunes punch me and call me gay all
the time. I must be super duper gay
then. Scrap says I act extra gay around
Roger and Shrimpo, which is funny cuz I
do feel my face getting hot when I'm
around them. Is that what gay is? Dear
Goob, can I have a hug, please? Only if
you give me a big bear hug back.
Question for Goob, my child. How much do
you like cookies? Cuz if you like
cookies a lot, here's one. Oh gosh,
thank you. Cookies are my absolute
favorite. If yours is even half as good
as Cosmos, I'm sure I'll love it. After
I eat it, I'll be sure to spit it back
out and mold it back together so that I
can give you one, too. Hey, Goob, what
age were you diagnosed with autism? I
still haven't been. I think even though
we know I got it, Scraps doesn't want me
to get officially diagnosed because then
it will be on record and it'll be a
forever reminder about how much her
brother is broken. I don't like that
others call me broken because I'm
autistic. But I guess I am. I don't
know. Goob, why do you love hugs so
much? Because tunes are depressed beings
by nature and nobody can be depressed
after they've been hugged. If I was
there when the World Trade Centers fell
on 9/11, you could only imagine how many
hugs I would be giving out. Dear Goob,
do you find Finn cute? I think he is. He
really is. More than just looks. He
makes cute noises, too, when I pull him
in for a tight hug. Dear Goo, what is
your favorite snack or food? If just
one, then dinosaur chicken nuggies. If
two, Skittles and dinosaur chicken
nuggies. Dear Goo, where did your tablet
go? The one that you use because you
have stutters or you have a hard time
talking. Do you mean my AAC unit? I
usually just take it with me if I'm
going places I know will have a lot of
people, like at a restaurant or standing
in lines. I don't just bring it
everywhere I go with me, though, because
walking down the sidewalk with it makes
people ask me what it does. And
explaining it makes me uncomfortable
because it takes a long time. Like it's
doing the opposite of what it's supposed
to be doing for me. Dear Goob, how does
it feel to know you're hated by
everyone, even by your own sister, just
because of your disability? If hating me
is what makes everyone happy, then I'm
happy. I do wish it wasn't at the
expense of hating me, though, because
that makes me a little less happy. Goob,
are you really a silly goober? My
silliness is my best quality. Goob, do
you and Shrimpo have kids? I'd love to
have kids someday. They're awesome. We
could color together and make macaroni
art. I just don't know where you're
supposed to get one. Shrimpo told me
they come after you hug someone for too
long. And when I asked Shrimpo if that
meant we were having one since I hug him
a lot and he said, "If we ever have
kids, we're getting an abortion." I
still don't know what that is. I thought
it was where you go to get the kid.
Hello, sweetie. You're the cutest thing
that's ever happened to this show. You
know that? By the way, I noticed that
you and Finn interact with Shrimpo quite
often, even though he's repeatedly been
mean to you. Neither of you deserve his
attention. How about you become friends
with Finn? He's a cool guy. You
definitely get along. Love you. But
Shrimpo's always been nice to me. He
yells really loud to make sure I hear
him. And sometimes he punches me in a
way that kind of tickles. It's his funny
little way of saying hi. I think Finn's
really cool, too, though. Even if he did
destroy the cardboard box my sister and
I were living in at the time, I'd love
to hang out with him and talk about how
much we both like Shrimpo. Oh, and thank
you. I love you, too. You're really
nice. Goob, is it true the furthest
number you can count to is three? That's
not true at all. I know so many more
numbers than that. I know A and B and C
and Huh. Maybe I do only know three.
Goob, are you still dating Roger? I
don't know if we ever officially started
dating. I asked him to be my boyfriend
one time and he told me not to fall for
an old man like him because he doesn't
have many years left. But I don't get
that because I think I could make those
years happy. Plus, me being 19 and Roger
being 67 isn't that big of an age
difference. I wonder if he's scared
because Shrimpo likes me and Dandy and
Astro. Oh, I can't help it that I've got
so many [__]
Dear Goob, you are my favorite character
in the show. Who cares what others think
of you? Because I have autism, too. And
having autism is a good thing because
your creativity is off the scale and
endless. Oh, yay. That's so cool. Thank
you. I think everyone has something that
makes them special. And autistic tunes
like us are just even more special. I'm
really happy you like me. That makes me
smile a whole bunch. I hope you keep
being yourself cuz I think you're
awesome, too. Big Goop hug. Goob, are
you a misogynist? A misogynist is where
you give people massages. Oh, I can be.
I want to be the best misogynist ever.
Goob, are you a good boy? I hope so. I
try to be the goodest boy there is.
Goob. Goob. Goob. Dear Goob, are you
still in love with Roger after the
sleepover, or are you just friends? Uh,
I don't really know. I want to get
closer to him, but he hasn't been
answering my calls.
Boxton, how did you control your
half-twisted state? Does it take control
for you or do you take control of it?
Also, why did you fight Astro and start
flirting with him like 2 days later? I
may or may not be hunting and
eradicating twisteds in my free time.
When I noticed Astro's arms were
dripping one day, I figured he must have
been going twisted, but it turned out
he's one of the few we call
half-twisteds, just like I am. Astro and
I are more in control of our emotions
than others. So, while Aker can fully
take over a stress tune and turn them
twisted, Astro and I can't be overtaken
by it. Have I been flirting with him?
Not on purpose. I haven't realized it
from my end, but I do have a habit of
becoming dense around cute things.
>> Dear Boxton, why do you have a weird
smirk like you're about to do something
that I won't get into detail?
>> Most tunes will go twisted when they
experience a traumatic event. I have an
affliction where my twisted form is
always turned on, just in the
background, and I have to keep it at bay
at all times. When I have dark thoughts
that would get me locked up if those
thoughts ever came out, a hint of
emotion from my twisted form can become
visible, even if I'm not necessarily
twisted yet.
>> Boxton, how did you get so cool and
inconfident?
>> When you know you've got the biggest
butt cheeks in a room and everyone's
looking, the cool and the confidence
comes easy. It's also important to be
kind and stand up to bullying whenever
you see it. Boxton, why are you so
goated and nonchalant?
>> I never started vaping because drugs
aren't cool. That's the reason. I would
never judge others for vaping though
because that's not my place and I don't
know what they are going through. If
they need help, I could maybe even help
them.
>> Boxton, do you keep snacks in your box
head? Like Doritos or off-brand Capri
Suns?
>> Absolutely. I've always got a
family-sized bag of Cool Ranch Doritos
in my head at all times. Not the
off-brand [__] though. I have far too
much worth in myself to buy anything
that isn't name brand or smaller than
the family size so I can share with my
friends.
>> Dear Boxton, does the music your head
play depend on your emotions?
>> I'm sure I could change the tune that
comes out of my head if I visited a
music box specialist, but for now it
only plays one song. I usually listen to
it before bed because hearing the same
tune every night has become part of my
routine. It's familiar and comforting
and I don't often let others listen to
it because it's my song. Boxton, how is
it like living with idiots?
>> It is a burden that I alone must carry.
I know that I am an alpha male above all
others, but I don't let it affect my
views on them as it would be ridiculous
to think every tune could be as
intelligent and sexy as I am.
>> Dear Boxton, would you and Astro be
considered friends? I've noticed you
interact a lot, or are you just curious
about him?
>> I would say the reason I find myself
around him often is a mixture of my
curiosity of him and his strangely
powerful tune ability and because he's
cute. because he's cute in an ugly way,
like one of those hairless cats. His
forearms make him look odd, even by tune
standards, and he always looks small and
pathetic in a way that it draws me in. I
think of us as friends, and I'd be
surprised if he didn't think the same.
>> Boxton, you often have that evil toothy
grin when under pressure or in a
competition. Because of this, do you
have any ambitions or plans plotting
against another tune?
>> As of now, I know the tune abilities of
myself, Astro, and a handful of others.
I also know which tunes can't and can't
control themselves when they give into
their twisted nature. And that's only a
select few. I can't deny that with the
knowledge I have, the thought of using
said knowledge to get whatever I want is
enticing to say the least. Boxton,
without spoiling anything to us, are
there other twisteds with far higher
ranked tune abilities that you're afraid
of facing against? Or are you confident
you could take just about anyone?
>> To be honest, my tune ability kind of
sucks balls. It's a C rank, so all I do
is like summon purple boxes and [__]
Compared to someone like Astro's S-rank
ability, which lets him rewrite reality
on a whim, mine is nothing. I'm sure
most others have abilities higher ranked
than mine, too. But it's how you use
them that matters. Any tune ability can
be overpowered in some way. I would just
need to figure out how.
>> Hey, Boxton, do you feel like a main
character when you boss everyone around?
>> I try not to stand in the spotlight
because that's not my place. So, not
really. I don't take pride in bossing
others around. I only do it when I have
to. I much prefer standing in the
background and not just because it gives
me an excuse to look at everybody's fat
butts. I love you, Box Tan. Do you love
me back? Sure, Astro. Oh, that was a
question. You know, if someone says they
care about me, the least I can do is say
it back. So, yeah. Take care of
yourself. All right, you sexy [__]
>> Boxton, where did you get that suit,
man? It looks nice.
>> The Goodwill. Boxton, what made you want
to be a therapist and how did you find
out about being half twisted?
>> I see tounes struggling often and if
they struggle too much, they will become
twisted and lose themselves. I thought
I'd become the therapist of Garden View
to try and help Tounes before they get
to that point. Simple as. As for how I
found out I'm half twisted, it's a story
I'm not comfortable with sharing because
it involves someone else who probably
doesn't want to be named.
>> Dear Boxton, how do you keep such a cut
figure? Like, damn. All the other tunes
are fat as hell, but you're shredded.
What's your secret?
>> I do a lot of squats. When the only
quality people try to make you known for
is the fact that your head is a box,
nobody would ever expect that box head
to have a six-pack and a big round butt.
Never let them guess your next move.
>> Boxton, do you have a crush on anyone?
>> No. Apparently, I'm the one people get
crushes on. I don't entertain them. It
only ends with hurt feelings. The
closest one I would say I could have a
crush on is a certain forearmmed thick
little [__] They're pretty enough, but
they carry enough baggage that I'd need
a luggage cart. So, so at the moment, I
strictly admire them from afar or swoop
in to save them so I can be their little
knight in shining armor just so I can
watch them get flustered.
>> Does it hurt to use your halft twisted
powers?
>> A little bit. Every time I make a funny
little purple box using my powers, I
feel what I can best describe as a pinch
on my brain. And if I use it too often,
I get a headache. I'd hate to find out
what would happen if I overuse my box
powers. So, I don't plan on ever doing
so. Hey, Boxton. Would you date Astro if
you had the chance? You're always nice
to him and stood up for him during the
boy sleepover.
>> At the moment, I'm content being single
because it means I can look at him from
afar without being burdened by what
comes from being in a relationship.
>> Thoughts on the other tunes? Are there
any that you'd consider as really good
friends or any that you dislike or hate?
Also, I love you. Can I have a kiss?
>> I don't dislike any tune unless I catch
them putting others down because I don't
like bullies. And even then, I am quick
to forgive tunes because there's no
denying that tunes by nature are corrupt
beings built by twisted Aker. Our
bitchiness is rarely ever our own fault.
>> Boxton, why are you wearing nice
clothes?
>> I used to walk around in nothing but a
bandana with my balls a swinging, but my
naked musical body was so smoking that
tunes were constantly walking into
street signs and breaking their teeth.
For their own safety, I decided to put
on clothes. It does get hot and I often
wish I could at the very least go free
balling like Cosmo. But it is a burden I
choose to bear.
>> If you had to choose either Finn and
Goob or Astro and Cosmo to take to
lunch, which two would it be and why?
>> I would like to have lunch with Finn and
Goob for the day. Mostly because there
seems to be some hostility between the
two of them and their equal feelings for
Shrimpo. I wonder if I can help them see
that Shrimpo is not the ideal catch for
either of them.
>> Boxton, which boys lover manga do you
like? And do you hang out with Blot? For
manga, I like the classics by Shungiku
Nakamura like Janjo Romantica and
Sakayichi Hatsukoy Given is a good one
too. Being that I am a music box, I have
a fondness for musical anime. I am also
a fan of Killing Stalking and
Heartstoppper and the rest of Alice
Osman's books if those count. And of
course, anything in the Omegaverse genre
is right up my alley. I love that Alpha
and Omega [__] I don't hang out with
Blot very much because he usually sticks
around with Louis and Yada, but I
imagine it would be a messy time since
he's always dripping ink like it was
diarrhea.
Who is your favorite tune? I don't have
a favorite tune. I only have tunes that
I don't like, but my favorite tune that
I don't like would probably be Finn
since he doesn't leave me alone. I hate
Goo a whole lot too, but he can be
tolerable, I guess. like when he makes
me cream puffs on days that I'm
especially mad.
>> Then uh which tune do you hate the most?
>> I hate everybody equally except for you.
I hate you the most for asking stupid
questions.
>> Shrimpo, how do you feel about Glisten?
>> Boys aren't supposed to wear makeup.
That's the rule. Pick a lame girly boy,
but Glisten is a boy who looks good in
it, and that makes me mad. One time he
let me borrow his black nail polish. Not
because I thought it would make me look
nice or anything. I just thought it
looked rock and roll. I hated it after
he put it on. I kept it on for only like
3 days. Dear Shrimpo, what is yours and
Finn's relationship like? I've been
trying to figure that out. Also, you two
are my favorites. I love whenever you
guys show up. It makes my day. Well,
Finn says we're friends, but we're not.
Okay. He's just the only one who doesn't
make a fuss whenever I hit him. And he's
the only one who listens to my
complaints about everything. AND HE'S
GOT A SMALL ASS, WHICH MAKES MINE looks
bigger by comparison when I'm standing
next to him. And of course, I'm your
favorite. I'm everyone's favorite.
>> How many bricks do you own? And do you
ever throw them at anyone? Or does Finn
ever make you use the maid dress?
>> I own so many bricks, you wouldn't
believe it. And Finn can't make me do
anything. That's not how this works. The
maid dress I own was made specifically
for him to remind him of his role in the
hierarchy when he's getting to
confident. When there's two boys, one
always has to be the girl. I've tried
putting it on and it's too big for me
anyway. I hate that it looks so
ridiculously good on him. I've mostly
seen you in metal mosh pits and gyms.
Why is that?
>> Because those places are awesome. In
mosh pits, people are always getting
tossed around left and right. And you
know damn well I'm right in the middle
of it causing most of the chaos. I've
never been knocked down in my life, so
you know I'm the strongest and coolest
there is. The gym is even better.
Nothing makes me happier than watching
everyone's spirit get crushed in real
time about how they will never be able
to lift as much as me, even when I poop
my pants while lifting.
>> Is your fur more like fur or like facial
hair?
>> It's a beard, obviously. I'm just so
manly it covers my whole face. Shrimpo,
why did you kiss Dandy? No one forced
you to do it. You could have ignored the
booth and just bought yourself a
McDonald's.
>> I guess I could have just gotten a Mc
Rib and a Dr. Pepper. But I can get
McDonald's every day already. I can't
taste dandy sugary sweet kisses every
day. And I'm not stupid enough to miss
my chance at tasting it. There is
nothing gay about being curious.
>> What do you smell like, boy?
>> Well, first of all, I'm not a boy. I'm a
man, so I smell like a man. The
smelliest and manliest of men ever,
obviously.
>> So, like, since a lot of shrimp turn
into females later on in life, is that
why you work out so much? To make up for
the fact that you have no pee pee
anymore,
>> don't talk like you know me. You don't
know what I got going on down there. You
don't know anything about me and leave
me alone.
>> Finn or Goob,
>> what? Like who I could take in a fight?
both at the same time. Obviously, they
can try and double team me so hard, but
I'll be the one left standing over them
by morning. Would you consider letting
both Goob and Finn impregnate you?
>> I think you've misunderstood who would
be the one in danger of that buddy.
>> Hi, Shrimpo. Anyways, how's it feel to
be the biggest baddest [__] with two
[__] by your side? I should say it's
a good feeling, but I'm not going to
rest until every tune in all of Garden
View has become Shrimpo's personal
[__]
Why does everyone hate you and want you
to shoot yourself in the forehead?
>> It's jealousy. That's what it's always
been. It's a burden I must carry by
being the most baddest shrimp ever.
Everyone on Earth becomes uncomfortable
when they witness peak shrimp
performance in front of them. They want
to be me so bad, but they never will.
>> Hey, Shrimpo, have you ever been nice to
anyone?
>> What could I possibly gain from doing
that?
>> Dear Shrimpo, if you had to marry Goob
or Finn, who would you marry?
>> I'll reluctantly play your stupid game.
It's not like Garden View will ever
legalize gay marriage anyway, as long as
Dandy is in charge. Not that I would
ever want to get gay married or
anything. I think if I was being forced
to gay marry someone, it would have to
be Finn since he's really good at making
sandwiches. He's basically roleplaying a
housewife already whenever he's at my
house. Goob would be my mistress who I
have sex with when Finn goes to work.
Hey, Shrimpo, do you hate hating or do
you love hating? Because if you hate
everything, do you hate hating?
>> Yes. I mean, no. I mean, I hate
everything.
>> Shrimpo, why do you think everything is
gay?
>> Because this is Dandy's world.
Everything in Dandy's world is gay.
>> Shrimpo, what do you think about Scraps?
>> I think she should be in the kitchen
making me a sandwich because she's a
woman.
>> Shrimpo, I'm your number one fan. You
are the best. You know it.
>> I know that. You're wasting the oxygen
around me by even saying it, [__]
>> Shrimpo, why you be mean to Finn? Is
someone making you do it?
>> No one can make Shrimpo do anything. I
do it because I can. Simple as when you
find yourself constantly around a
weak-willed [__] all the time. You'll
take advantage of them too with enough
time. Kicks this idiot off the edge of a
ninestory building.
Hey, Shrimpo. Why do you keep Finn in a
collar?
>> Because if I didn't, he would walk out
of my life just like everybody else. Not
that I'm looking for sympathy or
anything.
>> Dear Shrimpo, how do you honestly think
about Finn?
>> I think he's lucky. He's got a big butt
to make up for his his ugly misaligned
teeth and personality of a kindergarter.
But if you ask me, I think he got a BBL,
which would mean there is nothing
organically positive about him.
>> Why are you so abusive to Finn and make
him wear a maid dress most of the time
when he is around you? Maybe because he
looks good in it. Ever thought of that,
[__] I'm doing him justice by dressing
him up nice and cute. And I'm doing
myself what's good by making him stand
next to me while wearing it. Shrimpo,
have you ever considered drinking Finn?
>> Sometime I think about what it would be
like to fill his head with tomato soup.
Drink it straight out of the bowl. But
then I remember I sometimes use his head
as a piss bowl. And I have to remind
myself I shouldn't be drinking out of
there. Finn's head is almost always
filled with piss, but I drink a lot of
water, so my pee is clear and not
yellow, so nobody ever knows.
>> Shrimpo, do you actually care about
Finn? What do you feel or gain by
hurting him or not letting him go?
>> I don't care about anything. I just hate
Finn a little bit less than how I hate
everybody else. If I let him go, who
else would listen to me talk about how I
hate everything that's not him? Shrimpo,
if you had to choose one tune that you
hate more than anyone else, who would it
be? Only one.
>> Probably Roger. I know he is
particularly close to Goob. So, I make
it a point to not talk to him because if
that day ever came where we meet and
nobody is around, I would beat HIS ASS.
NOT THAT I'm jealous of Roger or
anything about his closeness to Goob. I
don't care about Goob at all. One time
Roger tried to unal alive himself by
jumping off a roof and he failed and
never tried to do it again. I think
that's a sign of weakness and as such he
is the weakest tune in Garden View. If
you intend to unalive yourself like a
little [__] at least go through with
it so you can leave your sexy
19-year-old twink follower like goob
open for anybody else to take. Not like
I want to date Goobb. It's just
whatever.
>> Hey Finn, what's your opinion on Goob?
Goob? What is there about him to even
have opinions about? I hardly even think
about the guy. Or how a lot of people
would say he's more handsome than I am.
Shrimpo likes standing around handsome
guys. So maybe that's why he wants to
spend so much time around Goob lately,
even though Shrimpo is supposed to be my
best friend. Not that that bothers me or
anything. I don't feel threatened by
Goob at all, Finn. Did Shrimpo knock
your tooth out? When I was trying to
soft launch my coming out to Shrimpo, he
was like, "You better not be trying to
hit on me, gay boy." And then he punched
me and I blacked out. When I woke up, my
tooth was gone, so I think maybe I
swallowed it. Dear Finn, are you and
Shrimpo dating? Golly, does it look like
we are? We're just best friends is all.
I mean, if you wanted to start dating, I
would probably say yes just to give it a
go. I never dated a boy before and I
don't think he ever has either. So, it
would be a learning experience for the
both of us. We're always together
anyway, so would it really be any
different than our normal routine of
going to my favorite fishing spots? Dear
Finn, you're my favorite character. I
also love fish. I used to be a boat
girl, but now I'm a horse girl. I draw
you a lot. And my question is, do you
like or maybe even love Shrimpo? And do
you know if he likes you back? Of course
I like Shrimpo. He's the best friend
I've ever had, and he must feel the same
for me. Otherwise, he would be spending
his time with some other tune, right? As
for love, well, uh, I'm hesitant to use
such a strong word, unless I know for
sure he'd use the same for me. Finn, how
did you get back your legs? Did you just
grow them back? It's hard to tell from
how flexible I am, but my body is made
of glass. After everything of mine below
the waist was blown off by Boxton, I
just had to get a new pair of legs made,
and everything was good. Dear Finn, how
do you feel about being my most favorite
tune in all of Garden View? BS, it's not
your fault. It never was. At least I'm
somebody's favorite. I'll be keeping
that in mind when I cut myself tonight
for Finn. I love you. Me and my child
loves you as a tune, of course. Anyways,
what's your favorite food? What hobbies
did you used to do? And is Barnaby still
in your head? My favorite food is kind
of boring. Fish and chips. When Shrimpo
and I go out to eat, he makes me share
with him whatever I order. So, I get the
fish and he gets the chips. As for
hobbies, is cutting oneself a hobby?
Huh? Uh, I actually keep Barnaby in a
fishbowl at home these days. I don't
want him getting hurt if Shrimpo just
randomly hits me in the back of the head
during one of his outburst. Finn, what's
your shoe size? Well, above average.
It's the only thing in my life I'm proud
of. Dear Finn, do you know that Shrimpo
likes Goob and not you? If so, then how
do you feel about this? It'll just be a
passing thing. I'm willing to let
Shrimpo flirt with other boys as long as
Shrimpo always comes back to his one
true friend. Even if Shrimpo wanted to
date Goobb is so mentally challenged, I
don't think he knows what dating is,
right? And Scraps is homophobic, so I
trust her to not let her brother date a
boy like Shrimpo. I have nothing to
worry about. No worries, dear Finn. If
it's not so intrusive, how did you
started selfharming? Have you also
considered being with someone who
doesn't mistreat you? One day, Shrimpo
and I were out in a boat fishing. It had
only been about 10 minutes before
Shrimpo got bored and wanted to be done
with it. He took the oars and started to
row the boat back to shore, but I tried
to stop him because I still needed to
reel in the fishing pole. At some point,
I sliced my arm open with a fishing
lure, and I didn't even realize until we
had gotten back to shore, and my arm was
covered in blood. Even though Shrimpo
blamed it on me, he helped bandage me up
and stayed over at my house a lot longer
than he usually did that night. Now he
complains when I do it on purpose, but
he helps me clean up. Dear Finn, are you
okay? I uh could be better, I think.
Dear Finn, why are you always near
Shrimpo? And why the heck do you have a
plushy of him? How many other
merchandise do you have of him? Shrimpo
doesn't always physically assault me.
It's only when I do something wrong. I'm
the problem, not him. And it's not weird
having plushies and shirts with the face
of someone you love. I just see it as
being their number one fan. Dear Finn,
are you a fanboy? I'm whatever Shrimpo
wants me to be. If that means being his
little fem [__] for the day, I'd gladly
do it. Finn, do you have water come out
of you and you pee? I've been told my
pee tastes a bit like ocean water. I've
tasted it myself and compared it to
other tunes pee, but I don't really
taste a difference. Finn, can you value
yourself a little more? Why are you so
fixated on something that's not worth
it? Before I cut myself, I would say I
had some value. But since my scars
aren't just going to magically
disappear, I think most would agree my
value as a tune plummeted. There aren't
many fish in the sea who want to be
friends with a tune with gross markings
all over his body. And the tune I'm
fixated on is the only one who thinks
having scars makes you a man. So, I'd
say what I'm fixated on is worth it.
Finn, why are you bad as hell? I think
you might be overestimating me. I'm
basically just surviving out here on
these streets. Dear Finn, are you
actually made of water or glass? Just a
random question. I am. I have to replace
the water in my head every week,
otherwise the glass will get foggy.
Finn, what's your favorite soup? And
Shrimpo, where were you on January 6th?
My favorite soup is tomato soup with
oyster crackers. And unfortunately, I do
have to say that Shrimpo and I were both
at the capital on January 6th. Shrimpo
was scaling the walls and it brought
Taco Bell in case he got hungry. He did
fall right on top of me and I dropped
the Taco Bell so we didn't get to eat
any of it. When we were leaving, we were
both quickly tackled by police and
that's the reason we're both on the
no-fly list. Finn, what would you do if
the Dandy's World Fat Acceptance Club
had their weekly meeting at your place?
I've tried sitting in on one of their
weekly meetings before and they
physically threw me out. I mistakenly
took it as a chubby chaser fan club. It
was Squirm who threw me out. And I can't
deny being manhandled by such a handsome
fatty did make my face all red. Dear
Finn, you are great and my favorite
tune. Would you ever aggressively crack
Shrimpo if you had the chance to? P.S.
Do you like my profile picture? I drew
it myself. Your profile picture looks
nice. Believe me, I would completely
destroy Shrimpo's little shrimp so hard
if you would let me. You have no idea.
That's all the questions we have for
today. Thank you to everybody who
submitted. And remember, if you didn't
see your question answer, a part two
will be coming very soon. Or if you're a
newcomer who wants to see your own
question show up here, too. Leave it
down below, as well as which tune your
question is for, and that'll make sure
it's answered in the next episode of
Dandy's World Q&A. If you want to be one
of Tamers 1 2 3 4 5's [__] and get
access to exclusive Dandy's World gifts
and episodes that are a bit too much for
YouTube to handle, go support Tamers 1 2
3 4 5's Patreon. And if you want to
support Tamers 1 2 3 4 5 on YouTube, be
sure to like, comment, and subscribe and
hit the bell so you know there are new
videos.